真不错啊  老兄  太绝了
Way to go, man, go! That was awesome.
你被打得惨绝人寰啊
They beat the crap out of you.
何足挂齿  都是即兴表演
It's okay. I did a lot of ad-libbing.
真对不起大家
Guys, I'm so sorry.
太谢谢你了  那演技太赞了
Thank you so much. That was amazing.
我也受益匪浅
Even I learned something.
-没事啦安妮  -我们成功了
- Oh, Annie. - We did it.
-群抱一个  -抱抱
- Group hug, group hug. - Hug, hug.
-好一记力挽狂澜  -干得好
- Way to save the day. - Nice work.
棒球伤到脸了没
Did you get hit in the face with a baseball?
有吧
Yep.
安妮  无需多言
Annie, before you say anything,
我只想你知道
I just want you to know,
虽然我并未做错
Even though I did nothing wrong,
但我还是要给你钱
I'm still gonna give you money.
我不能拿你的钱  皮尔斯
No. I can't take your money, Pierce.
我不能刚脱离对父母的依赖
I can't go from depending on my parents